In a northern town
lives a
southern...
I really can't drink anymore.
You bastards.
Li Zhangxin,
you again?
He Shi,
you don't even deserve to be human,
let alone a father.
Xique!
Xique,
stop smashing things.
This kid isn't even mine.
Help! Go away!
Get away from me!
Help! Get out of here!
Didn't you call the police?
You know,
as the richest family in Rongcheng,
any stir in the He family
is like front-page entertainment news.
If I called the police,
it would only humiliate the He family.
Are you willing to just suffer in silence?
If I hadn't gotten pregnant,
this could have been
covered up.
Then how did He Shi
find out?
Honey,
We're having a baby.
Tell me, whose is it?
Whose else could it be but yours?
Bullshit!
I'm completely infertile.
Since that day,
He Shi seemed like a different person.
It's not your fault.
You're a victim too.
I didn't want to keep him at first.
But the doctor said my health was poor.
I went to the hospital for a checkup
and was caught by paparazzi.
Mr. He, not knowing the truth,
wouldn't let me abort him.
This is his only eldest grandson.
He Shi
just agreed to it like that.
And so,
we kept him.
But all the terrible things
He Shi is doing now
are aimed at this child.
Maybe
he just can't get over it.
What's done is done.
What else can I do?
Most of the surveillance cameras
on that road
inexplicably broke down that day,
leaving only this footage.
Someone must have tampered with them.
Besides Zhang Xin,
who else wants me dead?
Why is Li Zhangxin here?
The family motto echoes
with profound meaning.
The butler is out of the way.
Next
are Zhang Xin and He Shi.
Good.
In the future,
you won't just be washing for Mrs. He...
You even have to wash your husband's.
She's pregnant,
so it's already hard
for her to get around.
We have so many maids at home.
Just let them do the washing.
My dear brother,
you're finally awake.
What,
feeling sorry for her?
Do you want her
to serve you too?
Since we're all part of the He family,
we should behave properly
and show the demeanor expected of us.
Dad isn't even here.
Who are you putting on this act for?
Mrs. He,
my sister-in-law didn't marry
into the He family
to wash your feet.
Did I force you?
Not at all.
I did it willingly.
He Yu,
thank you.
I'm fine.
Did you hear that?
Don't interrupt their fun.
Hopeless.
Come in.
Second Young Master,
you've been bedridden for so long.
Your body must be stiff.
Let me help you with some rehab exercises.
Okay.
What did you do before
joining the He family?
Going to school, of course.
I just graduated.
What were you doing
on July 4th?
Why are you asking about
such a specific date all of a sudden?
July 4th,
three months ago.
Is it the day you had the car accident?
Okay, okay.
I'll be right there.
A hit-and-run? Is this guy for real?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
I got it.
Could it be that
the one hit by the car
was my second brother?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Why is this hairstyle so unique?
Otherwise it'd be too boring.
Mei.
Ah!
It's nothing.
Why is your hair
different from everyone else's?
It'd be too boring otherwise.
Young Master,
you're in the wrong room.
Li Zhangxin,
isn't it time
we settled our score?
What score?
I just work for the He family
and they pay me, right?
Playing dumb with me?
If it weren't for you last night,
I wouldn't have embarrassed myself
in front of all those people.
You said those things
and made the mess yourself.
What does it have to do with me?
Besides,
didn't you ask Shu Roujing
to keep the baby
because
you were afraid Mr. He
would find out you're infertile
and cut you out of the will?
What are you laughing at?
If Mr. He finds out
that this grandson is a fake,
and that you lied to him,
what do you think he'll do?
I dare you to tell my dad.
Maybe I will.
Don't worry.
I'll kill you
before my dad gets back.
Let
go.
He Shi,
it's one thing to do
whatever you want outside,
but this is the He family.
How dare you hit your brother!
Stop fighting!
Stop fighting.
Fine, keep fighting.
Then I'll record this
and let everyone know
that the He family is at odds.
Are you okay?
Just protect yourself.
Honey,
time to wash your feet.
Why is it so hot?
I'm sorry.
I'll add some cold water.
Since you hope this child
will bring you benefits,
you shouldn't let anything happen to him.
You should treat
the eldest daughter-in-law well.
Otherwise,
Master He won't let you get away with it.
Wipe it clean.
Yes.
Li Zhangxin,
I will destroy you.
Come in.
Li Zhangxin,
gather everyone quickly.
The Master is back.
Hurry up. Move it.
Quick.
Is everything ready over there?
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Master.
Welcome back, Master.
Are you tired?
Was the journey exhausting?
Dad,